副总统官邸
VP Residence
非常感谢你安排了这次采访 Dan
Thank you so much for setting this interview up, Dan.
我很感激 完美 我的荣幸
I really appreciate it. It's perfect.  My pleasure.
瞧 很简单的一件事
Look, this is a walk in the park.
就是朋友间的随便聊聊 愉快的那种
This is a nice casual conversation between two friends.
今天 全美国都是你家的客人 - 欢迎光临 美国人民
Today, America is a guest in your home.  Welcome, America.
要记住 Janet比你更需要这个
The thing to keep in mind is Janet needs this more than you do.
大实话 我是说 她现在没那么红了
That is so true. I mean, she's kind of a lightweight now.
我们是在帮她的忙 - 她不中用了
We're doing her a favor.  She's a dud.
知道吗? 我们得做准备了 准备时间 去吧
You know what? We got to prep. Prep time, let's go.
好 - 那首得罪了半个欧洲的歌曲?
Okay.  The song that offended half of Europe?
那没有得罪半个欧洲
It didn't offend half of Europe.
好吧 成 我得说 Janet
Okay, fine. Well, I have to tell you, Janet,
那只是个轻松的戏仿之作
that was a lighthearted parody.
竞选游说时你和Andrew一直在微笑
On the campaign trail, you and Andrew were all smiles,
但背后你们俩就跟一山不容二虎似的
but behind the scenes you were fighting like snakes in a bag.
你是个骗子和说谎者 女士
You're a fraud and a liar, ma'am.
喔 什么? 你在做什么? - 我在攻击你
Wow. What? What are you doing?  I'm hitting you.
伙计们 我们准备的是吹捧式访问 可不是吐槽大会
Guys, we're prepping for a puff piece, not for a roast.
没错 顺便问 她穿什么?
Right. What is she wearing, by the way?
藏青色西装外套
She's wearing a navy jacket.
保守而绝望
It's conservative and desperate at the same time.
啊? 看我穿的是什么
What? Look at what I'm wearing.
我们知道她要穿什么吗? 能弄清楚吗?
Do we know what she's wearing yet? Can we find out?
我们马上就进去了
We are gonna go in there in just a moment.
他们等着我们吹捧 - 没错
They're expecting a puff piece.  Right.
开场我们假意吹捧一下
There's the bluff puff which we're gonna start out with.
你是她的朋友 你们上同一所高中
You're her friend. You went to high school together.
你们相互喜欢 然后马上切换到暗讽
You guys like each other. Then we switch right over to rough puff.
没人比你更会暗讽
Nobody does rough puff like you.
呃 就是那样的暗讽
Rrr. Give me that rough puff.
- 好吧 吹牛老爹 (艺人名 puff双关) - 唔
All right, Puff Daddy.  Ooh.
这人在干什么? - 他在移动一只没腿的马
What is this one doing? He is moving a legless horse.
哦 Catherine - Ryland小姐
Oh, Catherine.  Miss Ryland.
能见到你真是太荣幸了 - 很高兴见到你
It is such an honor to meet you.
-It's a pleasure to meet you.
我是你的大粉丝 - 谢谢
I'm such a fan of yours.  Thank you.
实际上我想学广播新闻
I actually am hoping to study broadcast journalism.
现在我学习的是影视研究和后现代舞蹈
Right now I'm studying film studies and postmodern dance.
真不错 拍摄开始的时候我们得聊聊这个 - 我会很高兴的
How wonderful. We'll have to talk about that  when the cameras are rolling.  I would love that.
我正在上一节很酷的课 课上我们通过动作来辩论时下议题
I'm taking this really cool class where we sort of debate current issues through movement.
来把你的麦克风装好 - 哦
Let's get you miked up.  Oh.
哦 天哪 这是个问题
Oh, my God. This is a problem.
瞧这个 - 你是说鼓鼓囊囊的么?
Look at this.  For the poof, you mean?
把你的手放口袋里
Put your hands in your pockets.
如果把手放口袋里 我看上去就像在自慰
Looks like I'm masturbating if I got my hands in my pockets.
用张毯子挡一下 还是那样太像罗斯福了? (有腿疾)
Put the blanket over it, or is that too FDR?
你们能跪下来吗?
Can you guys please kneel down?
因为我觉得我像是掉井底了似的 这让我脖子好痛
'Cause I feel like I fell into a well or something and it's hurting my neck.
好吧 他们会提到那个漂筏旅行
Okay, they're gonna bring up the rafting trip.
哦 我把我的前夫拖倒河里
Well, I took my ex down to the river
用石头砸他的头然后溺...
and I tried to smash his head in with a rock and then drown-
这是Cody Marshall
This is Cody Marshall.  Cody Marshall.
他是第一反应的制片人 - 你好 Cody Marshall
He's the producer for "First Response. "  Hi, Cody Marshall.
抱歉 我是否打扰了你们的集体祷告? - 只是高度调整什么的
I'm sorry, am I interrupting a team prayer meeting? We're just doing a height thing.
没什么 - 哦 祝好运 各位
It was nothing.  Okay. Good luck, everyone.
非常感谢 你真好心 谢谢
Thank you so much. Very kind. Thank you.
感谢你的到来 我们很感激
Thanks for being here. We really appreciate it.
好了 她穿的是一条蓝裙子 就好像她把花吐了满身一样
Okay, she's wearing a bluish dress like she vomited flowers all over herself.
她就像个邋遢的图书馆管理员 - 哦 好
She's kind of a frumpy librarian.  Okay. All right.
哦!太好了 我们有生意了 - 什么?
Yes! All right, we're in business.  What?
刚刚确认了有一封泄露邮件
Just confirmed a leaked e-mail.
她前夫为了商业利益承诺可以接近副总统
Her ex-husband promising access for business favors.
他真的在吹嘘这个 - 我知道
He actually brags about it.  I know.
这太讨厌了 - 吹嘘可以接近副总统
It's almost too painful.  Brags about access.
你先装友好让她失去防备 然后来个大反转狠狠地咬她几口
Just drag her in with the kindness, then turn great white and start taking chunks out of her.
她可不够我吃的
She's not much of a meal.
哦 是Greg?
Oh, is it Greg?  Gary.
Gary 我们都准备好了 所以如果你可以...
Gary, we're all set up, so if you can...
哦 好极了 嗯
Yeah, great. Yeah.
副总统女士
Madam Vice President.  Janet Ryland.
哦 我想我们最后一次见面是在...
Gosh, I think the last time that we saw each other was at the...
白宫记者协会年度晚宴 - 白宫记者协会年度晚宴
The Correspondents' Dinner.  The Correspondents' Dinner.
没错 我觉得你又长高了
That's right. I think you've grown since then.
不是那样就是你变矮了
Either that or you've gotten shorter.
哦 呃... - 不 是我 我穿了高跟鞋
Oh, well... No, it's me. I've got heels on.
哦 不管怎样 真高兴你能来
Well, anyway, I'm so happy you're here.
那么你觉得这里还成吧
So you found the joint okay.
哦 当然 我想这是我们第四次副总统访问了
Oh, yeah, I think this is our fourth vice presidential interview.
真的吗? - 嗯
Is that so?  Mm-hmm.
之前的三次都完美极了 所以不要有压力
The three of them were excellent, so no pressure.
他在对我说 - 哦
He's talking to me.  Okay.
那么计划是什么? 我们要做些什么?
So what is the plan, then? What are we going to do?
哦 我想我们首先会稍微展示一下这间屋子
Well, we'll start, I think, just with a little walk around the room.
然后是正式的访问 我想 就在这
And then the formal interview, I thought, right here.
哦 这里? 哦 - 是的
Oh, right here? Okay.  Yeah.
但那就是说这个得移开
But that means that this has to go.
我以为你们会在那边做
I thought you were doing it over there.
不 之前是 不过我们会在这里做 这里也很好
No, we did, but we're gonna do it here, and that's perfectly fine.
所以我们会把那倒霉玩意拿走
So we'll get that poor thing away.
随便了 你有见过我的女儿吗?
Anyway, have you met my daughter?
你真的收到了我最后一封关于讨论话题的邮件了吗?
So you did get my final e mail on topics?
没 但是我的垃圾邮件过滤器收到了 - 认真点 你收到了吗?
No, but my spam filter did.  Seriously, did you get it?
我有吗?
Did I?
嘿 都搞定了 让我们来创造历史吧 伙计们
Yeah, we're all set. Let's make some history here, folks.
好了 开始摄像
Okay, roll cameras.
十分感谢您邀请我们来您家 副总统女士
Thank you so much for inviting us into your home today, Madam Vice President.
哦 这是我的荣幸
Oh, well, it's certainly my pleasure.
我想 聊聊哪些是原装的
I thought it might be fun to talk about what's original
哪些是后来加上去的会很有意思
and what's been augmented over the years.
我们说的是这栋建筑 对吧?
We're talking about the building, right?
因为我就是原装的 - 您当然是
Because I'm original.  You certainly are.
不 没错 就是这栋建筑 女士 - 是的
No, yes, the building, ma'am.  Yes.
这栋建筑本身是安妮王朝式样 (18世纪英国的建筑和家具式样)
The building itself is Queen Anne style.
这当中的很多东-塞 呃 东西
Many of the objay-ects objects
事实上 都来自于海军中的老家伙们
are from the good old boys in the Navy, as a matter of fact.
真的? - Jolly Jack Tars (海军的昵称)
Really?  Jolly Jack Tars.
打个比方 这个 这个小望远镜 或者望远镜
For instance, this this spyglass here, or telescope-
能看到间谍
To see spies.
但愿吧? - 哦 既然您提到了
If only, right? You know, since you brought it up,
您介意评论一下
would you care to comment on the CIA operative
在乌兹别克斯坦被和学生一起解救的中情局特工吗?
rescued with the students in Uzbekistan?
哦 我真的 我不知道该说什么
Well, I really I wouldn't know what to say
因为此时调查仍没有结论
because at this point the investigation is pending.
这一件
Now this here
是一件令人惊讶的导航工具
is a stunning sort of navigational device.
我只是认为您大概会想说说
I just thought you might want to comment
他是如何使那些年轻学生的生命受到威胁的
on how he endangered the lives of those young students.
但是 我在调查之前做出判断
But it would be wrong and unethical
不但是错误的 也是缺乏职业道德的
for me to prejudge the investigation.
这个是铃
This is a bell.
我们能取些你和Janet在门厅里走过的景吗?
Can we get some shots of just you and Janet walking in the hallway?
当然 - 不取声音
Sure.  No sound.
我们只是取些远景
We're gonna just do some establishing shots.
我们会放上她的旁白 - 我们会在之后加上去
We'll put her voice over  We'll lay that in later.
哦 好 - 开拍
Yeah, okay.  And action.
哦 我想我们打过招呼 说间谍的事是绝对不能提的 对吧?
Yeah, I thought we said that the spy thing was completely off-limits, you know?
我很抱歉 在我看来
I'm sorry, it seemed to me-
我十分希望那会是
I'm really hoping that that's gonna be
最后也是唯一的陷阱问题
the last and only gotcha question.
只是我以为你希望我把它提出来
It just seemed to me that you were wanting me to bring it up.
不 一点也不
No, that wasn't the case at all.
我明白你为什么这么紧张 - 不 我不紧张 Janet
I understand why you're tense. No, I'm not tense, Janet.
连丝毫的紧张感都没有
I'm not even remotely tense.
只是不想让访问出岔子
Just trying to get this done right.
唔 - 这是以前某些人弄上的破玩意 我不知道是谁
Mm-hmm.  This is some old shit by somebody, I don't know who it is.
这房子闹鬼吗? - 哦 天哪 我不知道
Is this house haunted?  Oh, God, I don't know.
说实话 我讨厌这栋房子 就像生活在洋娃娃监狱里一样
I hate this house, to tell you the truth. It's like living in a doll's jail.
Cynthia 能给我些别针么? - 好的 来搞定它
Cynthia, could I get clips?  Okay, let's settle.
把背后清空 麻烦 - 这能凸显你的曲线
Clear the background, please.  Gives you a nicer line.
哦 是吗? - 你不需要别针 你的身材很棒
Oh, really?  You don't need clips. Your shape is great.
不过这个呢? - 哦 天哪
But what about this?  Oh, my God.
好吧 这儿 把它折起藏在下面 把手这样放着
Okay, here, let's tuck this under. Put your hands like this.
但这看起来像我胃在痛 - 非常感谢
But that looks like I have a stomachache.  Thank you so much.
好了 开拍吧
Okay, let's roll cameras.
每个人都准备好了 谢谢 Glen
Everybody settle in here. Thank you, Glen.
声音? - 在录音
Sound?  Sound speeding.
那么我们开始了
And we are rolling.
知道吗 我觉得有些暗
You know what? I'm feeling a little bit dark.
哦 就是想...
Yeah, just want to...
Gary 我们能把那灯弄过来吗
Gary, can we get that light back?
抱歉 请把灯移回去
Sorry, let's move that light back.
能给副总统几盏灯么?
Can we get a couple of lights for the vice president?
哦 我得临时从屁股里拉出来（想一想）
Yeah, let me just pull that out of my ass.
这里是特区 你可以找到周日会开放屁股的人
It's DC. You can find someone willing to open their ass on a Sunday.
很好 祝你好运 正在录音
Great, good luck. Sound is speeding.
每个人都各就各位了 他们看起来棒极了
Everyone is set and settled. They look great.
开拍
And rolling.
你有读过Randall Howard的书
Have you read Randall Howard's
《权力之心： 特区最有影响力的夫妇》吗?
Hearts of Power: DC's Most Influential Couples?
遗憾地说 我没有很多时间去读小说
Sadly, I don't have a lot of time to read fiction.
那么 在选举期间
Now, during the election,
有一些关于你和你前夫Andrew之间
there were reports of screaming matches
争吵的报告
with you and your ex-husband Andrew
还有那些微笑和感情的展示
and suggestions that the smiles and shows of affection
都是在摄像机前做戏的说法
were all faked for the camera.
你们的感情都是为了作秀吗?
Was your friendship all for show?
完全不是
Absolutely not.
瞧 Andrew陪着我去竞选游说
Now, Andrew was on the campaign trail with me,
是因为他真的认同 并且现在仍然认同
really, because he shared, and still does share,
我对美国未来的展望 - 哦
my vision for America.
Okay.
我们需要重新安排一下照明
-We'd like to reset for lighting.
我们要重设照明 - 很快
We're gonna reset for lighting.  Just a quick lighting reset.
还有说实在的 她可以结束Andrew这个话题换另外的
And, really, she can move on from Andrew.
我是说 她可以想问几次就问几次
I mean, she can push as much as she likes,
但是你们只会得到同样的答案 所以...
but you're just gonna get the same answer, so...
唔 你有看过电视新闻吗?
Hmm, have you seen television news before?
没有 不过我希望圣诞节的时候能得到一套设备
No, I am hoping to get the box set for Christmas, though.
听起来就是那样 - 嗯哼
That's what it feels like.  Uh-huh.
嗯? 抱歉
What? Excuse me.
哦 - 喂?
Okay.  Yes?
你在... - 过来
What are you  Come here.
为什么? 你为什么要打电话? - 过来一下
Why? Why are you calling me?  Come here.
天 你可能还想从他妈的报纸上剪两个洞窥视
Jesus, you might as well cut out eyeholes and peer through a fucking newspaper.
你他妈的在干什么? - 现在是世界末日
What the fuck are you doing? It's "Apocalypse Now. "
有封Andrew给说客的邮件
There's an e-mail from Andrew to a lobbyist.
他宣称可以提供接近Selina的最佳门路
He's claiming super access to Selina.
他在吹嘘 - 这个?
He's bragging about it.  This?
就是他妈的Andrew 哦
It's fucking Andrew, yeah.
副总统女士 - 嗯? 嗯?
Madam Vice President.  Yes? Yes?
你前夫Andrew有任何政治上的抱负吗?
Does your ex-husband Andrew have any political aspirations?
哦 天哪 - 我们得告诉她
Oh, my goodness.  We've got to tell her.
我们得告诉她 - 不行 不行 不行 别对Selina说一个字
We've got to tell her.  No, no, no, don't say anything to Selina.
为什么? - 因为Janet在这
Why?  'Cause Janet's right there.
你不认为我们在她耳边说的时候她会注意到?
You don't think she's gonna notice we're whispering in her ear?
然后她会赶紧让这个没种的男人去查
Then she gets on and she tells this dildo to look it up.
然后我们就有了个该死的故事 - 怎么了?
And then we have a fucking story.  What's going on?
Andrew又混蛋了 - 他从各个方面把我们弄得一团糟
Andrew's fucking us again.
-He's screwed us in all known dimensions.
什么新消息? - 另一个丑闻
What's new?  Another scandal.
对 但这是个他妈的很糟糕的破事 - 他就是政治毒药 他是政治
Yeah, but this is fucking bad shit. He's political poison. He's political-
你好 Andrew
Hi, Andrew.  Andrew.
他一生都在做商业地产
He's been in commercial real estate his entire life.
所以没有任何理由可能存在跨界的现象?
So there's no reason there would be should be a crossover?
哦 我当然无法 呃
Well, I certainly couldn't, you know,
替他回答这个问题
answer that question for him.
那么对不久前
Would it surprise you to learn that only moments ago
一个博客报道你的前夫
a blog has reported that your ex-husband
向某个说客承诺有接近你的门路的事情感到惊讶吗?
promised a lobbyist favorable access to your office?
这确实存在于一封来自你丈夫的真实邮件... - 哦 我知道了 哦
It does exist in an actual e-mail  from your ex-husband to..  Oh, I see. Okay.
你好 Jim 记得吗 我能直达天听
Hi, Jim. Remember, I have the vice president's ear
并且有各种接近她的门路
and I can get all kinds of access to her.
后面跟着一个眨眼的表情符号
And then there's one of those winking emoticons
就在结尾处
at the bottom there.
我猜那可能表示那是玩笑话
I'm guessing that that was meant as some sort of a joke.
你知道 Andrew Meyer对于我的决定没有任何...
You know, Andrew Meyer has no influence whatsoever
影响力
over my decision-making.
这很难相信 因为你刚描述了一种
It's hard to believe because you've just painted a picture
你们的关系非常亲近 极其亲近的画面
of your relationship being very close, extremely close.
我们没有心灵感应
We're not telepathically linked.
他读不了我的心 - 嘿 已经15分钟了
He can't read my mind.  Hey, that's our 15 minutes.
十五分钟到了 好 好
That's the 15-minute mark. Great. Great.
休... - 哦!休息一会 休息一会吧
Let's take a  Oh! Let's take a break,let`s take a break.
天!
God!
哦 - 你还好吧 Gary?
Okay.  Are you okay, Gary?
哦 哦 我很好
Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
抱歉 我能调整一下你的麦克风吗
Sorry, could I just adjust your radio mike?
我这里有些静电干扰 - 好了
I'm getting some static.  I got it.
喔 哇哦! 喂 我靠耳朵吃饭的
Ow! Whoa! Okay, my ears are my livelihood.
你不需要 - 哦 肯定
You don't need to  Okay, I bet.
好了 退开吧
All right. Let's just back off.
我知道现在你想杀了某个人...
I know that you want to kill somebody right now...
- 是的 - ...不幸的是那不能是这屋子里的任何一个人
Yeah.  ... but unfortunately it can't be anyone in the building.
好吗? - 好的
Okay?  Okay.
Selina告诉我谁会来采访我的时候 你就没法摆脱我了
When Selina told me who was gonna be interviewing me,
you couldn't keep me away.
等会再和你聊 - 棒极了
Talk to you a little later on.  Wonderful.
我很期待 - 我也是
I look forward to it.  I do, too.
不过先和我来一下 把你的形象处理一下
But let's take you now and get you all changed and fixed up.
我们结婚的时候 他在洗手间呆的时间比我还长
When we were married, he took longer in the bathroom than I did.
那不是事实 你为什么那么说? - 先进去
That's not true. Why would you say that?  Just get in here.
该死的这是什么? - 电线
What the hell is this thing?  That's a cable.
哦 去 - 有条电线
Oh, shit.  There's a cable.
听我说 你之前在想什么?
Listen to me. What were you thinking?
什么? 那只是玩笑
What? It was a joke.
又一次了 Andrew
Once again, Andrew, you have totally
你又让我大失所望
lived down to my expectations.
我邀请你来官邸来做爱的时候 我没有这个意思
When I invited you here to the residence to fuck me, I didn't mean this.
我们不是在互相利用吗? - 你在说什么?
Aren't we using each other? What are you talking about?
好吧 我仔细说明一下
Okay, I'll spell it out for you.
美利坚合众国的副总统
How easy is it for the Vice President of the United States
要临时来场性爱有多难 嗯?
of America to get some casual sex, hmm?
我很方便
I'm convenient.
还有 我知道 - 让我告诉你
And, I know  Let me tell you something.
没错 我是美利坚合众国的副总统
That's right, I am the Vice President of the United States
而我决定不再和你做爱
and I choose now not to fuck you anymore.
时间会证明 我得换衣服
Time will tell. I've got to change.
是 你看起来糟糕极了
Yeah, you look awful.
你很漂亮 - 住口
You look wonderful.  Stop it.
啊哼 他就上去换个衣服
Ahem, he's gonna go just change.
等等 他去哪里? - 去拿我的东西
Wait, where's he going?  To get my stuff.
在我的卧室
In my bedroom.
哦 不 唔嗯
Oh, no. Uh-uh.
哦 Andrew有和副总统上床? 你知道?
Oh, Andrew's been veep-fucking? You knew about this?
好吧 这是他妈的最高级风暴
Okay, this is a category five shit storm.
她结束了 她完了 我走了
She's over. She's done. I'm gone.
唔 我在想是否能拍些Andrew进来的远景
Um, I'm wondering if we can get just a shot of Andrew's entrance just for establishing.
你们在这碰头 亲一亲 嗨 嗨
So you guys meet here, kiss, kiss, hi, hi.
就是家人聚在一起
It's a family getting together.
不 不 我了解什么是登场以及如何和人打招呼 我知道了
No, no, I understand what an entrance is and how to greet people. I get that.
很好 哦 他来了!
That's great. Oh, here he comes!
不 不 不 等等 等等 等等
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
不 不行 你们不能拍这个 抱歉 我们不能做这个
No, no, you're not gonna get this. I'm so sorry. We're not gonna do that.
我们可没有那种Seuss博士的书里描写的在阁楼的前门
We don't have a front door in our attic like in some sort of Dr. Seuss book or something.
有时候拍摄这些毫无准备的场景 就会引起紧张
Sometimes filming these off-guarded moments, things get a little tense.
哦 不 这压根不是紧张
Well, no, it's not tense at all.
我们度过了美妙的时光 而我很高兴你们能来 但是请按规矩来
We're having a great time and I'm thrilled you guys are here, but let's just do it the right way.
嗨 爸爸
Andrew!  Hi, Dad.
你怎么样? 很高兴见到你 抱歉
How are you? Nice to see you. Excuse me.
你好吗? - 很高兴见到你
How are you?  Nice to see you.
爸爸 - 嗨 你好吗?
Dad.  Hi. How are you?
这大概多久一次? - 哦 天哪
How often does this happen?  Oh, gosh.
每周一次我们聚在一起聊聊天吃吃饭什么的
Once a week we get together for a gab and a gobble.
是的 哦 我是说 你知道 如果时间什么的允许
Yeah, well, I mean, you know, schedules permitting and stuff
因为我现在真的当做自己和副总统办公室结了婚
because now I really consider myself to be married to my vice presidential office.
我是说 最近Mary King和我
I mean, recently Mary King and I were working
日以继夜地工作来避免这次停工
through the night to avoid this shutdown.
当然那没有 那没有成功 很遗憾
And of course it wasn't it wasn't avoided, sadly.
您认为您本来可以更努力一点吗?
Do you think you could have worked a little harder on that?
哦 我们一直很努力
Well, we are working harder.
令人丧气 当然 - 当然
It's frustrating, of course.  Sure.
对美国民众来说的确如此 - 这是个很漫长的过程
To the American people it is.  It's a very long process.
(敲门声) J大牛在
Knock, knock, J Rock is in the-
喔 喔 喔 - 我们正在摄像中
Whoa, whoa, whoa.  We're in the middle of filming.
哦 天哪 Jonah - J狗狗 J狗狗
Oh, my goodness, Jonah.  J Dog. J Dog.
您好 帅小伙 你好吗? - 你好吗?
Howdy, handsome. How are you?  How are you doing?
嘿 Jonah - 很高兴再次见到你
Hey, Jonah.  Great to see you again.
天 你长大了 哼?
God, you've grown up, huh?
在你生日派对上我度过了美妙的时光 - 不错
I had a great time at your birthday party.  That's great.
很高兴见到你 嘿 怎么样?
Great to see you. Hey, how's it hanging?
Jonah是我们的 亲爱的Jonah是我们的白宫联络人 - 是我
Jonah is our dear Jonah is our White House liaison.
Guilty.
他是西翼里最有趣的人中的一个
And he's one of the more colorful characters in the West Wing.
当然 那是个让人印象深刻的入场 - 哦 谢谢 我试图一鸣惊人
I'll say. That was quite an entrance. Oh, thank you. I try to make a mark.
我就想说我是你的狂热粉丝 顺便说
I just want to say I'm a huge fan, by the way.
我由衷地喜欢你的节目 - 谢谢
I love your work genuinely.  Thank you.
还有 实际上 我要给你我的名片 万一你想要任何形式的
And, actually, I'm gonna give you my card just in case you ever need any sort of, like,
就像西翼内部揭秘那种的
inside the West Wing kind of stuff.
我偶尔会在媒体上曝光 我很能说
I do occasional media appearances. I give great talking head.
Jonah 我们能知道您驾临的原因吗?
Jonah, to what may we owe this pleasure?
哦 我刚刚结束和白宫的通话
Oh, I just got off the phone with the White House
15分钟内总统将宣布停工结束
and in 15 minutes POTUS is going to announce that the shutdown is over.
真的吗? - 那不是很棒?
Is that true?  Isn't that great?
那不是很棒? - 镜头拉近到她身上
Isn't that great?  Move in on her.
没错 议长 参议院多数党领袖还有总统
Yeah, the Speaker, Senate Majority Leader,
他们达成了一致 我们让美国再次运转起来了 - 啊嗯 是的
and POTUS, they thrashed out a deal  and we switched America back on.  Uh-huh, yes.
恭喜 副总统女士 - 谢谢
Congratulations, Madam Vice President.  Thank you.
我们做到了 我们做到了 你做到了
We did it. We did it. You did it.
这个决定比你预计的早
The resolution took less time than you anticipated.
哦 所有的努力都是为了此刻
Well, it took all the time leading up to this time.
那么你今天预期能解决? - 是的 没错
So you were expecting a solution today? Yes, I was, yes.
但你刚刚说那会是一个漫长的过程
And yet you said it was going to be a long process.
那的确是 没错 那是
And it was, yeah. It was.
你有参与...
Were you involved in the-
Janet 这就像你拧松了一个泡菜坛 然后有人过来打开了它
Janet, it's like when you loosen a pickle jar and somebody comes by and they just open it.
这就是拧松停工盖子的人
This is the shutdown lid loosener.
拧松泡菜坛盖子的人 - 我喜欢
The pickle jar loosener.  I like it.
哦 不过你能和我们讲讲这最终协议的事情吗?
No, but can you talk us through the final agreement?
我能 它 你知道
I can it's you know-
我能...但我也想用些午饭
I can and I also want to eat some lunch.
我们饿了吗?
Are we hungry?
唔唔 肯定的 - 没错 去吃午饭吧
Mm-hmm, definitely.  Yeah, let's get some lunch.
暂时停拍 是的 我想这暂时停拍了
That's a cut. Yeah, I think that's a cut.
午餐时间 - 暂时停拍
Lunchtime.  That's a cut.
哦 她不 - 哦 天哪 她不知道
Okay, she doesn't  Oh, my God, she didn't know.
那让我想起了我入行的原因
That reminded me why I got into this business.
我现在太为你着迷了
I am so attracted to you right now.
我就坐在这里然后看你们准备
I think that I'd like to just sit back and watch you all prepare this meal.
假装我不在这 - 唔嗯
Pretend I'm not here.  Mm-hmm.
我就是墙上的苍蝇
I kind of want to be the fly on a wall.
哦 天哪 Andrew 你弄得到处都是
Oh, my God. Andrew, that's getting everywhere.
唔 我得给你一只...
Um, I'm gonna get you a...
削皮器 好吗? - 我不需要削皮器 谢谢
peeler, okay?
I don't need a peeler. Thank you.
哦 你需要个削皮器 - 事实上 不
Yeah, you need a peeler.  Actually, I don't.
哪里 我在试图记起在哪 你知道那种你明明知道你厨房里有某样东西
Where I'm trying to remember where you know how sometimes you have something in your kitchen,
你知道它在哪 但突然就找不到了的情况吗?
you know where it is, and then all of a sudden you can't find it?
那就是我现在的情况
And that is what's happened to me right now.
哦 你大概有太多员工在这进进出出了吧
Well, you probably have so much staff in and out of here-
不 不 不 我了解这厨房就像了解我的手背一样
No, no, no. I know this kitchen like the back of my hand.
哦 不是这个
Oh, that's not it.
好吧 我不知道哪里
Okay, I don't know where-
这令人恼火 你有过这样的经历吗? 想找到什么但...
This is maddening. Do you ever have this happen to you where you're-try to find that
我不在这 - 好吧 你不在 抱歉
I'm not here.  Okay, you're not here. I'm so sorry.
我在自言自语 你在哪 削皮器? 哦 找到了
I'm talking to myself. Where are you, peeler? Okay, I got it.
费解的 它居然和纸巾放在一起
It was in with the napkins inexplicably.
给 用来刨胡萝卜
Here you go. Use that for the carrots.
事实上 我弄完了 我好了
Actually, I'm all done. I'm good.
好吧 - 说说 你难道不是通常让工作人员为你提供饮食吗?
Okay.  Tell me, don't you normally have staff  to cater for you?
没错 完全正确 - 哦 当然 不过我也喜欢捣鼓锅碗瓢盆
Yeah, definitely. Well, sure, but I just love banging the pots around.
我觉得我是个美食家
And I think you would say that I'm a foodie.
那么 只是提醒你一下
So, just to flag with you,
很明显 Andrew显然是不能问的 (离开饭桌)
Andrew's obviously off the table.
哦 技术上来说他现在完全是在桌旁啊
Well, technically he's very much at the table currently.
有些什么菜?
What's on the menu?
香草烤鸡
Herb roasted chicken
还有些芝麻菜沙拉
and some arugula salad.
Catherine 你喜欢你们做的东西吗?
Catherine, do you enjoy your folks' cooking?
哦 我喜欢他们做的蔬菜
Yeah, I love the way that they cook the vegetables.
我最爱的永远是蔬菜
The vegetables are always my favorite.
我只是太喜欢蔬菜了
I just love vegetables so much.
你为蔬菜说客工作吗?
Are you working for the vegetable lobby?
我马上回来 我得去取些东西
I'll be right back.I just have to grab something.
好的 宝贝
Okay, darling.
拜托 你能用那个削皮器吗?
Please, can you use the peeler?
我搞定胡萝卜了 - 哦 天哪
I'm all done with the carrots.  Oh, my God.
不 你没有 - 我们要用的胡萝卜就那么多
No, you're not.  That's all the carrots we're gonna use.
我知道还有多的胡萝卜
I realize there are more carrots.
我们不需要更多
We don't need any more.
那个动起来运动
The Get Moving campaign,
如你所知的 我是领头人 - 没错
which as you know I spearheaded.  Yes.
在我发起那项运动的时候
As I launched that campaign, I discovered
(Catherine是素食者)
CATHERINE IS VEGETARIAN!
我发现了一个当地的卖有机肉的肉商
a local organic butcher.
还有...
And...
他养了许多...
he does a lot of...
她三个月前就告诉你了
SHE TOLD YOU 3 MONTHS AGO!
用草料喂养的...
grass-fed...
用草料喂养的牛
Grass-fed cattle
还有放养的鸡 - 是的 是的
and free-range chickens.  Yeah. Yeah.
你等不及要吃的最爱是哪道菜?
What's your favorite meal that you can't wait to have?
我十分 我十分喜欢我妈和我爸做的...
I really I love the roasted brussels sprouts
烤球芽甘蓝
that my mom and dad make.
是的
Yep.
好了 他们去休息了
Okay, well, they're taking a break,
这让我们有机会在这谈一谈
so this gives us a chance to come in here, have a little chat.
你从未告诉我你是素食者
You never told me that you were a vegetarian.
我三个月前就告诉你了 - 不 你没有 Catherine
I told you three months ago.  No, you didn't, Catherine.
什么? - 现在她提到了 我想这听起来有些耳熟
What?  Now that she mentions it,  I think it does sound familiar.
完全是废话
It`s completely useless.
知道吗? 就因为他是个麻烦 不代表你也得是个麻烦
You know what? Just because he's a liability doesn't mean you have to be a liability, too.
我告诉你 你得吃鸡肉
Now I'm gonna tell you something. You're eating that chicken.
我不会做的 我是素食者 妈妈
I am not gonna do it. I'm a vegetarian, Mom.
你一生都在吞咽鸡肉
You swallowed chicken your entire life.
- 今天你得再这么做 - 我一辈子都在忍受(吞咽)你的破事
You're gonna do it again today. I swallowed your bullshit my entire life.
好了 瞧 小淑女 我们不对你妈那么说话
Okay, look, little lady, we don't talk to your mother like that.
好吧 我只是 去他妈的
All right, I'm just God damn it.
你能不能... - 是的 是的 是的
Could you  Yes, yes, yes.
你知道你十二岁刚刚戒掉那个的时候?
You know when you're 12 and you just get rid of it?
不 你才那么干了
No. Speak for yourself.
如果在电视上她不知道你是素食者 你妈妈看起来会非常糟糕
It's gonna look really bad for your mom if she doesn't know that you're a vegetarian on TV.
我不会再为她的事业牺牲我的道德坚持了
I'm not gonna sacrifice my morals for her career anymore.
我做了 不是那么糟
I've done that. It's not that bad.
哦 你不觉得那鸡肉看起来很棒么 Catherine?
Well, doesn't that chicken look just amazing, Catherine?
它看起来很美味 - 耶
It looks delicious.  Yeah.
我喜欢我爸做的
I love it when Dad cooks.
一个有隐藏才能的男人 - 我不爱吹嘘
A man of hidden talents.  I don't like to brag.
反正吹的也不是做菜 唔 - 哦 宝贝 好了
Not about cooking, anyway. Okay, babe, here you go.
哇哦 - 吃光它
Wow.  Eat that up.
我得和你重申一次 我们在所有的采访内容上都达成了一致
I just need to reiterate with you. We have agreed on all of these topics.
Andrew邮件的事情并不在内
And the Andrew e-mail story was not agreed.
甜心 这是新闻
Sweetheart, it's news.
好吗? 今天刚发生的 是新的 后面还接了个s (new加s)
Okay? It happened today. It's new with an S on it.
这就是新闻 - 恕我直言 这不是新闻
That's just what news is. With all due respect, this is not news.
你看到的是他妈的美食频道
This is the fucking Food Channel you got here.
好吧 哦 恕我直言 操你妈的
Okay, well, with all due respect, fuck you.
我是你心心念念的这个破政治节目
I own the edit on your shit-show politician that
我想怎么剪怎么剪 你个小妖怪
you connected yourself to, not me, you little gremlin.
对你而言 你乐意他们离婚吗 Catherine?
And has it been a happy divorce for you, Catherine?
唔 是的
Mmm, yeah.
我想知道我妈得24小时待命
I think knowing that my mom had to be available 24 hours a day
实实在在地教会了我别像个孩子一样要求太多 - 那是事实
really taught me not to be too demanding as a child. That's true.
所以你并不觉得在父母爱上有短缺 是吗 Catherine? - 没有
So you don't feel parentally shortchanged, then, do you, Catherine?  No.
我实际上是个狂热的音乐爱好者 所以我试图用音乐概念来描述我的父母
I'm actually a big music fan, so I usually try to explain my parents in terms of music.
你知道的 音乐家们有时候组成乐队更好
You know, musicians sometimes are better in bands
有时候独唱为佳 - 有意思
or sometimes better solo.  That's interesting.
比如说披头士 你知道 是乐队的时候更好 或者Michael Jackson 独唱更棒
They're like the Beatles, you know, better as a band or Michael Jackson, better solo.
虽然不是很好的家长 不可否认
Although not a great parent, admittedly.
哦 实际上 他对自己的孩子还不错
Well, actually, he did okay with his own kids.
当有其他孩子的时候就变得很怪了
It's when other kids got involved that it got real dicey.
但是 不 他有在很高的地方 将某一个孩子悬空(迈克杰克逊的著名事迹)
But, no, then he did dangle that one from a great height.
对吧 在栏杆外?
Right? Over that railing?
要是你在这个问题上惹毛了我
You know, you cross me on this
你将永远 永远别想让副总统再接受采访了
and you're never, ever gonna get the veep on camera again.
他妈的为什么 你为什么还在跟我说话 哼?
Why the fuck why are you still talking to me, huh?
如果你还想让别人贴近你 然后日点快乐气息到你身体里
If you'd just let someone get close enough to fuck some sunshine into you,
你最好闭上嘴!
you'd shut your mouth!
你...你... - 好了 好了
You you  Okay, okay.
你根本一点也不了解我 你觉得我做的事情很简单?
You do not know anything about me. You think that this is easy, what I do?
没错 让一万个利益相关人士 用我现在对你吵吵的方式
Yeah, having 10,000 interests screaming in your fucking face
整天整天对着你他妈的脸吵吵怎么样?
the way that I am screaming in your face right now all day, every day?
我他妈的对这很拿手 - 我们能放个过滤器...
I am fucking good at this.  Can we just put a filter-
你是吗? 这很棒? - 操你丫的脸 Gary
Are you? This is good?  Fuck your face, Gary.
她对此很在行 伙计们 抱歉 - 操你丫的脸 你听到了?
She's good at this, you guys. Sorry.  Fuck my face. You hear that?
古董窗子 降下来
Antique windows. Bring it down.
他妈的刚刚发生了什么? - 古董窗子 降下来
What the fuck just happened?  Antique windows. Bring it down.
Amy 到这边来找回你的优雅 好吗
Amy, let's go find your dignity over here, okay?
让她滚出去 他妈的门外汉
Get her out of here. Fucking amateur.
好吧 好吧 - 嘿 别 别 别 别
All right. All right.  Hey, no, no, no, no.
别 真的 - 不 喔 好吧
No, seriously  No. Whoa, okay.
哦 听着 你得冷静下来
Okay, listen, you need to calm down.
至少我还关心这个事 你一整天都死气沉沉的
At least I am giving a shit. You are flatlining all day.
好吧 好吧 但是她今天有任何出彩的地方吗?
Okay, okay. But has she been impressive at all today?
瞧 我为她的表现做了张图表 好吗?
Look, I've graphed her performance, okay?
看这个 看这个漂亮的小图
Look at this. Look at this nice little graphic.
这是时间 这是他妈的她的事业
Here's time, here's her fucking career.
现在或许这儿该有一个小上升
Now maybe there should be a little uptick
因为她没有把食物吐得满桌都是 我不知道
because she didn't barf her food all over the table, I don't know.
那么如果她不能将这场他妈的破秀扭转过来 猜猜
So if she doesn't turn this fucking shit-show around, guess what,
我不知道我会怎么做
I don't know which way I'm gonna bounce.
Amy 当我超级疯狂的祖母发现自己控制不住的时候
Amy, when my memaw used to find herself getting snappy,
她会唱她最爱的歌 (Dixie's land)
she would sing her favorite song.
哦 我多希望仍在那片棉花田里
*Oh I wish I were in the land of ???
过去的时光不会被遗忘 看向远方
*We are not forgot look away
看向远方 看向远方...
*look away, look away...
哦 伙计们 拜托
No, guys, please.
最爱的家庭休假?
Favorite family vacation?
冲浪漂流 - 意大利
White water rafting.  Italy.
迪士尼乐园 - 到底是哪个?
Disneyland.  Which is it?
不 宝贝 我们从来没去过迪士尼乐园
No, honey, we didn't ever go to Disneyland.
哦 不 你没有带我去 Rosa带我和她的家人一块去的
Oh, no, you didn't take me. Rosa took me with her family.
谁是Rosa?
Who's Rosa?
她是... - 她是...
She was a...  She was...
帮佣 - 帮佣 对的
housekeeper.  Housekeeper, that's right.
你常和帮佣呆在一起?
You spent a lot of time with your housekeeper?
是的 她就像
Yeah, she was like a-
我们有去印度 - 唔
We did go to India.  Mmm.
印度之旅糟透了 - 唔?
India was awful.  Hmm?
我不知道你为什么不早点给我这个
I don't know why you didn't give me this earlier.
我不想在采访开始前给你
I didn't want to give it to you before your interview.
天 你不想喝点水吗? - 不 我很好
God, you don't want any water?  No, I've gotten good at it.
瞧 我本该强调我的成功
Look at this. I was supposed to be stressing my successes.
我却坐在那里塞了满嘴鸡肉
Instead I'm sitting there stuffing my face with chicken.
这儿的东西棒极了 伙计们 好家伙 大拇指
Great stuff in there, guys. Good stuff. Thumbs up.
Andrew在摄影机里看起来棒极了
Andrew looks great on camera.
从我的楼梯上滚下去 Jonah - 哦 是的 女士
Get off my stairs, Jonah.  Oh, yes, ma'am.
女士 - 什么?
Ma'am.  What?
我得对您直言 可以吗? - 什么?
I need to give you some straight talk right now, okay?
-What?
您对今天会怎样荒废掉的最糟糕的猜想
All of your worst fears about how this day could have possibly gone...
- 哈? - ... 成真了
Yeah?  ... have come true.
哦 天哪 - 不 不 抬头 看着我
Oh, my gosh.  No, no, up here. Look at me.
您想主宰这个访问? - 没错
You want to own this interview?  Yeah.
说出来 - 我要主宰它
Say it.  I want to own it.
很好 这是你要做的 你得做点大的
All right, here's what you're gonna do. You're gonna do something big.
你要做些大胆的举动 而你会在未来的5分钟做到
You're gonna do something bold. And you're gonna do it in the next five minutes.
这个怎么样? 我提起裙子
How about this? How about I lift up my dress,
让大家好好的一睹春光)?
give everyone a big fat shot of my cooch?
苍天啊 - 一切正常吧?
Jesus Christ.  Everything okay up there?
你需要更多的鼓励吗? - 不 开始吧
You need more pep talk?  No, let's do it.
他听到了? - 没有
Did he just hear that?  Nope.
使用原力  女士
Use the Force, ma'am.
我都不知道那是什么意思 - 出位的大动作 你指什么?
I don't even know what that means. Big and bold. What do you mean?
俄克拉荷马州来的混编歌么? - 听着 我是试着让她振作起来 好吗?
Like a medley from "Okla" fucking-"homa"? Look, I tried to wake her up, okay?
我别无选择 只能他妈的出击了
I have no choice but to be the fucking curveball.
棒极了 好了
Fantastic. Okay.
那么开拍 声音
Let's roll cameras. Sound.
哦 我有个多么美好的下午
So, what a lovely afternoon
能和第二家庭一起
I have gotten to spend with the Second Family.
那不错吧? 没错
How about that? Yeah.
Catherine 你会支持你的父母重新在一起吗?
And, Catherine, would you vote
for your parents to get back together again?
不 不 不 这样的话 我可以从
No, no, no. This way, I get a Christmas
他们两个人那里分别获得圣诞还有生日礼物
and a birthday present off of each of them.
Catherine 这对你处理关系/感情
Catherine, how does all this affect
有什么样的影响?
how you approach relationships?
没多少 我正处在很不一样的生活阶段
Not terribly much. I'm in a very different phase of my life.
你知道 我男朋友和我还很年轻 没怎么谈过婚姻
You know, my boyfriend and I are very young and not really talking about marriage.
是Rahim?
And this would be Rahim?
是的
Yes.
是个很有趣的名字
That is an interesting name.
是印度名字吗? - 是伊朗的
Is that Indian?  It's Iranian.
伊朗名字? - 他是第二代美籍波斯裔
Iranian?  It's second generation American Persian.
打电话给Tel Aviv (以色列港口)
Calling Tel Aviv now.
他受到你家的欢迎吗?
And has he been welcomed into your home?
没有
No.
只是因为那是 那就是个临时的事情
Only because it's just it's a casual thing
实际上已经结束了
and it's actually ended.
真的吗? 很遗憾听到这个消息 甜心
Really? I'm sorry to hear that, honey.
没什么 - 说到关系
That's okay. Speaking of relationships-
Andrew 抱歉 我只是需要问你
Andrew, I'm sorry, I simply have to ask you
关于你和说客Jim Melita的关系
about your relationship with lobbyist Jim Melita
还有你能提供接近副总统门路的暗示
and the implication that you offered access to the vice president.
哦 呃 那个...
Yeah, um, it's-
呃 简单来说
um, in a word-
嘿
come on.
或许我可能
Perhaps it's possible
高估了自己的力量
that I have overplayed my hand.
哦 我想可以这么说
Well, I think it's safe to say
Andrew手伸得太长
that Andrew overreached
说了些蠢话 没错
and just said something silly. Yeah.
我想副总统
I suppose that the vice president
也会同意
would also agree that
她说她有参与国家安全事务
when she said she was in the loop over national security,
也可能同样有些夸大
that also may have been an bit of an exaggeration.
事实上我不确定两者有可比性
I'm actually not sure that those two situations are comparable.
我相信有
I believe that they are.
由于你在调查结束前拒绝评论间谍指控和人质处境
And insomuch as you refuse to comment on the spy allegations or the hostage situation
我 同样的 也要回避
until the investigation is complete, I, too, would like to refrain
直到我找出我被指控说过
until I find out just exactly what it is
或者没说过的究竟是什么
I'm accused of having said or not said.
你应该明白这听起来像是你在拖延时间
You do understand that sounds like you're playing for time
而且实际上是在掩盖着什么?
and actually are hiding something?
抱歉 这是给我还是Selina的问题?
I'm sorry, was that a question for me or Selina?
我想是给我的
I think that question is for me.
我想说说间谍的事情
I want to talk about the spy.
那个中情局特工
The CIA operative.
不 不 -  是的 是的
No, no.  Yeah, yeah.
有个失败的沟通是我想替政府表示歉意的
There was a miscommunication for which I want to apologize
on behalf of the administration.
你知道 误导美国人民从来都不是我们的意图
You know, the intention was never to mislead
但那是它的结果
the American people, but that was its effect.
去 - 为此 我很抱歉
Shit.  And for that, I really am truly sorry.
但我要说我完全了解间谍的状况
But I am saying that I had full knowledge of the spy's status.
但她没有 - 我知道
But she didn't.  I know.
副总统女士 这是个很重大的坦承
Madam Vice President, this is quite an admission.
唔 现在我已扮演起一个
Mm-hmm. I have taken on a role now,
在国家安全事务中的重要角色
an important role in national security
我为担起此职责而骄傲
and I take great pride in that responsibility.
瞧 有时你需要采取行动
Now, sometimes you have to act.
而你总是需要倾听
Always you have to listen.
因为在政治中
Because in politics,
骨气与心灵的高度
a backbone and a heart
取决于你的耳朵
are only as good
有多棒
as your ears.
而我靠我的耳朵生活
And my ears are my livelihood.
好了 到此结束 伙计们
Okay, that's our segment, guys.
结束了 很好 很好 好了 - 那不错
That's it. Great. Good. Okay
That's good.
副总统女士 这是个很棒的访问
Madam Vice President, that was an amazing interview.
哦 非常感谢 从停工结束开始
Well, thank you very much. You're gonna take the spotlight back
你会重新受到众人瞩目 我能确定
from the end of the shutdown, I'll tell you that.
看着吧 - 好运 Andrew
We'll see.  Best of luck, Andrew.
很高兴见到你 - 祝所有的...好运
Good to meet you.  Good luck with all the...
加油 Meyer之队
Way to go, Team Meyer.
怎么样? 不错吧?
How about it? Right?
恭喜 - 诚实地说 那是
Congratulations.  Honestly, that was-
意料之外的 妈妈
that was something else, Mom.
很抱歉我提到了Rahim
I'm really sorry that I brought up Rahim.
我知道你不想让我那么做
I know you didn't want me to do that.
知道吗 我很遗憾你得将他抛弃
You know what? I'm sorry you had to dump him on the air.
关于访问的笔记 只是想帮你密切留意那些...
Notes about the interview. Just want to help you keep an eye out for those.
滚出去 - 你怎么样?
Get out of here.  How are you doing?
我吐露了太多的破事 我需要薄荷糖(双关 好东西)
I spewed out so much bullshit, I'm gonna need a mint.
他妈的薄荷糖 - 你需要薄荷糖?
A fucking mint.  Do you want a mint?
我去拿薄荷糖 - 不 我说的不是那个
I'll get you a mint.  No, I don't mean it.
我只是得回去以防任何人需要我 - 西翼
I'm just gonna head back if anybody needs me West Wing.
没人会 Jonah - 没人需要你 Jonah
No one does, Jonah.  No one needs you, Jonah.
是的 女士?
Amy.  Yes, ma'am?
Andrew走了吗 - 他走了
Did Andrew leave?  He's gone.
你能看看他是不是还在外面?
Can you see if he's still out there?
他忘记夹克了 - 哦 你的夹克还在上面
He just left a jacket.  Oh, your jacket is up here.
他的夹克 - 我在这等?
His jacket.  I'll wait here?
女士 你需要 - 不 没什么
Ma'am, do you need  No, it's fine.
我知道他的东西在哪
I know where his stuff is.
他们要...来胜利一炮?
Are they gonna... it's like a victory fuck?
他最好下来
He better come down.
他会下来吗? 我们需要等他吗?
Is he coming back down? Do we need to wait for him?
我们可以 - 我们很好
We got it.  We're good.
好吧
Okay.
我父母呢? - 唔
Where are my parents?  Um...
我爸走了吗? - 他们在 他们在谈话
Did my dad leave? They're having they're having a talk.
他们在楼上谈话 - 楼上谈话?
They're having a talk upstairs.  A talk upstairs?
他们大概要给你些什么 - 哦 天哪
They might be getting you something.  Oh, Jesus Christ.